{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"60","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"90","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"30","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"350","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"25","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"90","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"60","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"150","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"25","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"80","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"30","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"125","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"140","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"60","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"175","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"75","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"120","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"80","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"40","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"150","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"125","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"175","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"175","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"140","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"150","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"180","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"140","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"25","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"150","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"25","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"250","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"75","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"60","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"60","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"25","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"80","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"120","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"150","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"250","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"40","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"140","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"75","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"125","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"150","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"80","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"70","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"60","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"140","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"90","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"90","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"120","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"150","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"350","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"125","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"75","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"40","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"60","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"125","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"150","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"150","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"70","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"250","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"75","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"75","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"150","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"40","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"120","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"40","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"125","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"160","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"450","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"40","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"125","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"90","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"225","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"75","hint":"Сколько процентов?"}]}
